https://www.stuartrental.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
The Bay Area's Party & Event Rental Experts
COVID-19Facebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowInstagram page opens in new windowPinterest page opens in new windowYelp page opens in new window
Home ProductsNew Additions Bars Chairs China Cooking Decorations Draping Flooring Furniture Glassware Lighting Linens Serving Flatware Staging Tables Tents Wedding & Garden
ServicesParty Rentals Private Parties Tent & Canopy Rentals Construction Tent Rentals Event Planning Corporate Event Rentals Wedding Rentals Schools & Non-Profits Caterers and Hoteliers Social Distancing Solutions
ResourcesEvent Portfolio Product Photos Ideas Blog FAQs Equipment Instructions Stuart Price List
AboutCareers Core Values Customer Reviews History Press Releases & Awards
LocationsSouth Bay Showroom East Bay Showroom
Contact
Privacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices.
Information Collected
All information collected or submitted on The Stuart Rental Company web site are as follows:
Name
Company Name
Billing Address/Delivery Address
Email Address
Phone Number
IP Address
Use of Information
The information that you have provided when placing a quote request will be used in order to complete that request.  Your information will not be shared with any third parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.
Your e-mail address will be used to communicate with you and to send rental quotes/reservations to you.  You may also be added to our e-mail list in which you will receive promotions, newsletters, or surveys.  You can easily unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link when you receive our e-mail.
Other Web Site Links
This web site contains links to other web sites that are not the responsibility of The Stuart Rental Company. Please be aware that The Stuart Rental Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites.  Upon leaving our site, take precaution to read the privacy policy of other web sites.  This privacy policy applies solely to information collected from this web site.
Use of Cookies
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive.  Cookies can help a web site recognize previous visitors and remember any preferences set during those visits. Cookies can securely store your profile, personalize your user experience, and help us understand the types of products or services you’re interested in.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to prevent acceptance of cookies.
Data Security
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When sensitive and personal information is submitted on our web site, we take every measure to ensure that your information is protected both online and off-line.
How To Contact Us
Should you have any questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at feedback@stuartrental.com
Notification of Changes
If any changes are made to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted on our Privacy Policy page to inform our users regarding what information will be collected and how we use it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from what was stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice to accept or decline any new method(s) of information use.  All information will be used in accordance with the privacy policy under the time at which the information was collected.
Go to Top
IMPORTANT ANNOUNCEMENT REGARDING COVID-19
The Stuart Rental Company’s highest priority is the health and safety of our team members, clients, and their families. Therefore, we are taking this opportunity to set forth how we are managing our business operations during the COVID-19 pandemic.
We will continue to update our policies as we learn more from the medical and scientific community, including new information from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. We encourage everyone to frequently refer to the CDC website for the latest on how best to contain and mitigate the impact of the virus.
OUR SHOWROOM IS OPEN
LIMITED HOURS: 10:00AM to 2:00PM, MON-FRI
CLEANING AND SANITATION
We have enhanced the process and increased the frequency of our equipment cleaning, spending extra attention to regularly contacted surfaces.
– We are using the same chemicals on our equipment as hospitals use to disinfect their surfaces.
– In addition, we continue to launder all linens and disinfect dishware, silverware, and glassware with high-temp commercial dishwashers, industrial sanitizers and chemicals.
– These processes are done in compliance with the latest California state and federal CDC guidance to ensure our products are COVID-19-free following their cleaning.
– We are cleaning our showroom, offices, warehouse and common areas with greater frequency using hospital-grade disinfectants, paying special attention to frequently touched surfaces.
– We have curtailed all non-essential employee travel to minimize the risk of spreading the virus to our staff and among the general population and we have instructed employees who feel ill to stay home and consult their healthcare provider.
DELIVERY AND PICKUP PROTOCOL: 10:00AM to 2:00PM, MON-FRI
We are keeping our teams current on all recommendations and updates from the CDC as well as instituting new safety precautions for the pickup and delivery of any product.
– We have equipped our delivery and pickup teams with masks, nitrile gloves, hand sanitizer, and EPA-approved cleaners/disinfectants specifically recommended by the CDC in its Environmental Cleaning and Disinfection Recommendations.
– During pickups and deliveries, we wipe all products with all-purpose cleaning solution and a disinfecting cleanser.
– Nitrile gloves are carefully disposed of after every pickup.
– We have instructed our staff to follow CDC-recommended social distancing guidelines, including avoiding shaking hands and using proper hygiene etiquette including hand washing.
We are committed to doing what is necessary to curtail the impact of COVID 19 and will therefore update these policies as the CDC and local and state health officials issue more guidance.
CLICK HERE TO LEARN MORE ABOUT STUART’S SOCIAL DISTANCING SOLUTIONS FOR YOUR NEXT EVENT!
×
Request a Quote or Free Consultation
With an ever expanding inventory, Stuart's expert planners can save you time and money by quickly finding just the right rental products for your next event!
*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*CompanyMessageAdd AttachmentAttachmentJoin Our Newsletter?
Please add me to your Newsletter!
PhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Phone*CompanyMessageAdd AttachmentAttachmentJoin Our Newsletter?
Please add me to your Newsletter!
EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
Join Our Newsletter!
Stay up to date with the latest product announcements, event planning tips and promotional offers from Stuart Event Rentals!
*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*CompanyPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
Join Our Newsletter!
Stay up to date with the latest product announcements, event planning tips and promotional offers from Stuart Event Rentals!
*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*CompanyEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Phone*CompanyMessageAdd AttachmentAttachmentJoin Our Newsletter?
Please add me to your Newsletter!
NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
×
